OK, ready golf means when you've hit your ball, and you're getting ready to hit the next ball, whether you're riding in a cart, or walking, you should already be thinking what you should be doing.
So that way, when you get to the ball, you already have the right club picked out, and you're ready to hit the ball.
One of the biggest problems in golf today, is people are like, well I don't know what club to use, so they go and grab twenty different clubs, and then they talk with their friends, and then they get a swing lesson, so golf is taking too much time to play.
So if your time is valuable, as I think everybody's is, be ready to hit the ball when you get to it.
And that way, you'll be hitting the ball, you'll get a nice rhythm going, and the round will be that much faster.
So, ready golf is a good part of etiquette.
So, if you're playing with a foursome, each player should have their shots already planned in their minds so they all fan out and go to their balls.
Instead of you go to one player's ball, and then you go to the next player's, and the player's, and the next player's.
Because every time you waste five minutes, time is four shots per hole, times eighteen holes, you can play, it can take you seven hours to play.
So, who has time for that?
So, ready golf is really a serious part of good golf etiquette, it means, and it's good for your game, because you're getting a rhythm, and you're not waiting all the time.
So, be courteous to the people that are behind you, and be courteous to your group, and be ready to play every time.